[
  { "question": "house (n) \n/haʊs/", "answer": "ngôi nhà" },
  { "question": "apartment (n) \n/əˈpɑːt.mənt/", "answer": "căn hộ" },
  { "question": "building (n) \n/ˈbɪl.dɪŋ/", "answer": "tòa nhà" },
  { "question": "floor (n) \n/flɔːr/", "answer": "sàn nhà; tầng" },
  { "question": "roof (n) \n/ruːf/", "answer": "mái nhà" },
  { "question": "wall (n) \n/wɔːl/", "answer": "bức tường" },
  { "question": "ceiling (n) \n/ˈsiː.lɪŋ/", "answer": "trần nhà" },
  { "question": "window (n) \n/ˈwɪn.dəʊ/", "answer": "cửa sổ" },
  { "question": "door (n) \n/dɔːr/", "answer": "cửa ra vào" },
  { "question": "gate (n) \n/ɡeɪt/", "answer": "cổng" },
  { "question": "balcony (n) \n/ˈbæl.kə.ni/", "answer": "ban công" },
  { "question": "yard (n) \n/jɑːd/", "answer": "sân" },
  { "question": "garden (n) \n/ˈɡɑː.dən/", "answer": "vườn" },
  { "question": "garage (n) \n/ˈɡær.ɑːʒ/", "answer": "nhà để xe" },
  { "question": "stairs (n) \n/steəz/", "answer": "cầu thang" },
  { "question": "staircase (n) \n/ˈsteə.keɪs/", "answer": "cầu thang bộ" },
  { "question": "lift (n) \n/lɪft/", "answer": "thang máy (BrE)" },
  { "question": "elevator (n) \n/ˈel.ɪ.veɪ.tər/", "answer": "thang máy (AmE)"},
  { "question": "living room (n) \n/ˈlɪv.ɪŋ ˌruːm/", "answer": "phòng khách" },
  { "question": "bedroom (n) \n/ˈbed.ruːm/", "answer": "phòng ngủ" },
  { "question": "bathroom (n) \n/ˈbɑːθ.ruːm/", "answer": "phòng tắm" },
  { "question": "kitchen (n) \n/ˈkɪtʃ.ən/", "answer": "nhà bếp" },
  { "question": "dining room (n) \n/ˈdaɪ.nɪŋ ˌruːm/", "answer": "phòng ăn" },
  { "question": "toilet (n) \n/ˈtɔɪ.lət/", "answer": "nhà vệ sinh" },
  { "question": "hall (n) \n/hɔːl/", "answer": "hành lang/tiền sảnh" },
  { "question": "corridor (n) \n/ˈkɒr.ɪ.dɔːr/", "answer": "hành lang" },
  { "question": "attic (n) \n/ˈæt.ɪk/", "answer": "gác mái" },
  { "question": "basement (n) \n/ˈbeɪs.mənt/", "answer": "tầng hầm" },
  { "question": "chimney (n) \n/ˈtʃɪm.ni/", "answer": "ống khói" },
  { "question": "fence (n) \n/fens/", "answer": "hàng rào" },
  { "question": "driveway (n) \n/ˈdraɪv.weɪ/", "answer": "đường vào nhà" },
  { "question": "path (n) \n/pɑːθ/", "answer": "lối đi" },
  { "question": "porch (n) \n/pɔːtʃ/", "answer": "hiên nhà" },
  { "question": "terrace (n) \n/ˈter.əs/", "answer": "sân thượng" },
  { "question": "roof terrace (n) \n/ruːf ˈter.əs/", "answer": "sân thượng trên mái" },
  { "question": "laundry room (n) \n/ˈlɔːn.dri ˌruːm/", "answer": "phòng giặt" },
  { "question": "study room (n) \n/ˈstʌd.i ˌruːm/", "answer": "phòng học, phòng làm việc" },
  { "question": "sofa (n) \n/ˈsəʊ.fə/", "answer": "ghế sofa" },
  { "question": "armchair (n) \n/ˈɑːm.tʃeər/", "answer": "ghế bành" },
  { "question": "table (n) \n/ˈteɪ.bəl/", "answer": "cái bàn" },
  { "question": "desk (n) \n/desk/", "answer": "bàn làm việc" },
  { "question": "chair (n) \n/tʃeər/", "answer": "cái ghế" },
  { "question": "bed (n) \n/bed/", "answer": "cái giường" },
  { "question": "wardrobe (n) \n/ˈwɔː.drəʊb/", "answer": "tủ quần áo" },
  { "question": "drawer (n) \n/drɔːr/", "answer": "ngăn kéo" },
  { "question": "cabinet (n) \n/ˈkæb.ɪ.nət/", "answer": "tủ nhỏ, tủ để đồ" },
  { "question": "bookshelf (n) \n/ˈbʊk.ʃelf/", "answer": "kệ sách" },
  { "question": "mirror (n) \n/ˈmɪr.ər/", "answer": "gương" },
  { "question": "lamp (n) \n/læmp/", "answer": "đèn bàn, đèn ngủ" },
  { "question": "chandelier (n) \n/ˌʃæn.dəˈlɪər/", "answer": "đèn chùm" },
  { "question": "fan (n) \n/fæn/", "answer": "quạt" },
  { "question": "air conditioner (n) \n/ˈeə kənˌdɪʃ.ən.ər/", "answer": "máy điều hòa" },
  { "question": "carpet (n) \n/ˈkɑː.pɪt/", "answer": "tấm thảm" },
  { "question": "curtain (n) \n/ˈkɜː.tən/", "answer": "rèm cửa" },
  { "question": "pillow (n) \n/ˈpɪl.əʊ/", "answer": "gối" },
  { "question": "blanket (n) \n/ˈblæŋ.kɪt/", "answer": "chăn" },
  { "question": "sheet (n) \n/ʃiːt/", "answer": "ga trải giường" },
  { "question": "bathtub (n) \n/ˈbɑːθ.tʌb/", "answer": "bồn tắm" },
  { "question": "shower (n) \n/ˈʃaʊ.ər/", "answer": "vòi sen" },
  { "question": "sink (n) \n/sɪŋk/", "answer": "bồn rửa" },
  { "question": "fridge (n) \n/frɪdʒ/", "answer": "tủ lạnh" }
]

